LAGHLIMI OTHMANE

FRONT END DEVELOPER

+212614096392

laghlim.othmane@gmail.com

Bouaakaz Marrakech,

Portfolio

SUMMARY

Holder of a Bachelor's Degree (3 years) in Computer Systems and Software Engineering, I am currently looking for a stable job. I have two years of experience in front end web development, this job is my passion, because I am a responsible person. I have a driving license, I have a great sense of relationships, I like working in a team.

SKILLS

• HTML

Express

Sass

PHP 5

CSS

• Node.is

• SEO

MongoDB

JavaScript

Bootstrap

WordPress

• MySQL

React.js

• GIT, GITHUB

• SQL

WORK EXPERIENCE

Freelance event coordinator

2021 - Present

Developed a web application CRUD
 Using: React, Express JS, MongoDB, Node JS

 Developed a responsive web application for school Using: React, Express JS, MongoDB, Node JS

 Developed responsive clothing web site that contain dynamic content depending the users choice
 Using WordPress and WooCommerce.

Developed responsive web site for panel solar society
 Using: HTML CSS JS (link).

 Developed responsive IPTV services web site that contain dynamic content

Using: WordPress (link).

Developed my responsive web site portfolio
 Using: HTML, CSS, JavaScript.

Developed a web application for a car parts sales agency
 Using: Bootstrap4, JavaScript, PHP5.

Private School Teacher (ANNAJAH Group)

2018 - 2021

- Office application trainer (Word, Excel ...) for other Teachers.
- o Computer science education at the elementary and middle school levels.

Internship within OCP, IT and Telecom department April (2017)

 Creation of a trainee management application Using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP5.

Internship within the company ZYDCOM

April – May (2016)

 Creation of a customer management web application for a milk center Using: HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript and CakePHP.

Internship at the OASIS training and solution KNOWLEDGE August (2015)

Creation of a representative website Volkswagen models
 Using HTML, CSS, JavaScript and PHP5.

EDUCATION

Professional license (Bachelor's Diploma 3 year equivalent) 2016 - 2017

Graduate school of technology (Cadi Ayyad University), ESSAOUIRA Branch: Computer systems and software engineering

<u>University Degree in Technology (Pre-university DEC equivalent)</u> 2014 – 2016

Graduate school of technology (Cadi Ayyad University), ESSAOUIRA Branch: Computer systems and software engineering

Bachelor's Degree (CEGEP equivalent)
2013 – 2014

TASSAOUT High School, Kelaa Des Sraghna

INTERESTS

- GYM
- Running
- Cooking activities
- Reading

LANGUES

• Arabic

• English

• French